# **Christopher Dickson**

171/7 Easter Road Edinburgh

EH6 8LF

07384261886 | chrsdickson231@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/chris-dickson-7294a323a/

## **PROFILE**

Over the past 4 years I have been working on achieving my honours degree in web design and development. I do still enjoy cooking but have been able to focus on my education. I have varying skills and experience working in all sorts of different kitchens.

#### **KEY SKILLS**

HTML/CSS Digital Design Time Management
JS 3D Rendering Knife Skills
React UI/UX Design Cookery skills.
PHP/SQL Vector Illustration Programming

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### The Bonnington Bar Edinburgh

Jun 2023 to March 2024

The Bonnington bar in Edinburgh is a small pub situated on Bonnington road. There I worked as a chef and was mostly in charge of the kitchen when the head chef was off.

- Menu creation
- Prep and cookery.
- Stock count and ordering.
- Deep cleaning
- Training.

#### **Ergon Equine Internship**

Jan 2023 to May 2023

Ergon Equine are a small saddle making company outside of Edinburgh. They needed someone to come in a create a website that would be easy enough for them to continuously update themselves.

- HTML/CSS
- WordPress & Elementor
- UI design
- Database building

Chef | Hua Han Nov 2019 to Feb 2020

Hua Han is a small independently run restaurant in Edinburgh that both cater to sit in and take away diners.

- Preparing and cooking Asian meals per specifications
- Full clean down and deep cleans of the kitchen.
- · Preparing Asian sauces for use
- · Counting stock and ordering more when needed
- I was also in charge of some light admin work.

Head Chef / Kitchen Manager | Starbank Inn (Green king Pubs Ltd)

Dec 2016 to Sep 2019

Green king Pubs is a chain brand of pubs and restaurants across the UK. Starbank Inn is a small but highly awarded pub in the New Haven part of Edinburgh.

- Was given full kitchen control.
- I oversaw managing a small team of chefs and kitchen porters.
- I also trained new starts in the company policies and standards as well as all kitchen elements.
- I had to count stock weekly and order new stock twice per week.
- I also had to make sure that all my staff were allotted hours to accommodate their personal lives.
- I came up with weekly cleaning and fortnightly deep cleaning schedules.
- I got the opportunity to create menu items and was allowed to be creative.
- I managed to bring the business from having a food waste deficit per week back to having little to no waste.

# Head Chef / Kitchen Manager | Hanover Tap/ Jekyll and Hyde

May 2013 to Dec 2016

The Hanover tap formerly Jekyll and Hyde is a bar/restaurant on Hanover Street Edinburgh.

Page 1

Christopher Dickson

- With Hanover tap I was trained in pizza making.
- I conducted management training in Stirling and Glasgow and trained new starts from all over the UK.
- I had full control of the kitchen and oversaw creating and maintaining cleaning rota's, weekly schedules, stock counting and control, time sheets and maintenance of the kitchen.

## Game Tester | Rockstar North

Jun 2012 to Apr 2014

Rockstar North is a game company located in Edinburgh. Creators of the GTA games.

• I was given the opportunity to test GTA V a year before release. I was very lucky to have received this position. With this post, I was responsible for bug testing and reporting, play through testing, reporting to developers, logging issues on the company intranet, excel spreadsheets.

# **EDUCATION & QUALIFICATIONS**

# Edinburgh Napier University – BSC(Hons) Web Design and Development

2024

Pending

2:1 Predicted

2022

# **Edinburgh College - HND Digital Design and Development**

Achieved

### **INTERESTS**

I enjoy art and spend my spare time either designing in 3d or creating comic art within photoshop. I enjoy cooking in my spare time and love to learn new recipes.